Guide to the Nathaniel Gage Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Nathaniel Gage papers
1948-2001
SC0153
Gage, N. L., (Nathaniel Lees), 1917-2008
93.25 Linear feet
Correspondence, drafts, and notes related to non-Stanford professional activities; teaching materials and departmental files; student files kept by Gage regarding his graduate students; SCRDT administrative records as well as files of scholars, conferences, associations, labs and publishers; organizations represented include American Psychological Association, American Council on Education, American Educational Research Association, and the National Society for the Study of Education. Also includes correspondence, memos, and minutes, 1983-1989, pertaining to the journal TEACHING AND TEACHER EDUCATION.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Gift of Nathaniel Gage, 1976-2003.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
Professor of education and psychology at Stanford since 1962, co-director of the Stanford Center for Research and Development in Teaching (1965-1968) and chairman of SCRDT's Executive Board (1968- ).
Description of the Collection
Correspondence, drafts, and notes related to non-Stanford professional activities; teaching materials and departmental files; student files kept by Gage regarding his graduate students; SCRDT administrative records as well as files of scholars, conferences, associations, labs and publishers; organizations represented include American Psychological Association, American Council on Education, American Educational Research Association, and the National Society for the Study of Education. Also includes correspondence, memos, and minutes, 1983-1989, pertaining to the journal TEACHING AND TEACHER EDUCATION.
Access Terms
American Council on Education.; American Educational Research Association.; American Psychological Association.; Gage, N. L., (Nathaniel Lees), 1917-2008; Gage, N. L., (Nathaniel Lees), 1917-2008; National Society for the Study of Education.; Stanford Center for Research and Development in Teaching.; Stanford University. Graduate School of Education. Faculty.; Stanford University. Graduate School of Education.; Education, Higher.
Collection Contents
- Original Accession
  - NATHANIEL GAGE PAPERS
    - American Psychological Association Committee on relations between psychology and education., 1956 Sep (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Programs and working papers for conference.
    - American Psychological Association: Task force E., 1961-62 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Correspondence: 4/61 - 6/66.
      "Report of ad hoc task force E to the Board of Professional Affairs of the A.P.A."
    - Association for Supervision and Curriculum Development - Center for the Study of Instruction: Seminar on Teaching., 1965 May (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Gage, N.L.: "Research on cognitive aspects of teaching"
      Correspondence: 12/64 - 8/66
      Rosenshine, B.: "Rough comments on cognitive aspects of teaching"
    - Associated Organization for Teacher Education. (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Gage, N.L.: "Psychological theory and empirical research for teacher education."
      Correspondence: 9/63 - 9/64.
    - Geneseo, New York, State University College., 1965 Nov (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Correspondence: 3/65 - 5/67.
    - Great Cities School - University Teacher Education Project. (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Gage, N.L.: "Desirable behaviors of teachers."
      Correspondence: 8/64 - 4/65
      Ellis, Richard: "Looking toward desired behaviors in teachers of the disadvantaged."
      Gordon, Edmund: "Desired teacher behavior in schools for socially disadvantaged children."
      Steward, Charles: "Compilation of responses regarding successful teacher behavior in inner city schools."
      "The development of school-university programs for the pre-service education of teachers for the disadvantaged through teacher education centers."
      Pittsburgh Study: "Promising teachers behavior for use among culturally disadvantaged pupils."
    - Illinois Statewide curriculum study center for the preparation of teachers of secondary school English., 1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Correspondence: 6/64 - 1/65.
      Reports of the conference.
    - National Council of Teachers of English., 1963 Nov (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Gage, N.L.: "This side of paradigms: the state of research on teaching English."
      "Research design with special reference to the teaching of English."
      Correspondence: 7/63 - 6/64.
    - National Society for the Study of Education Yearbook: Theories of Learning. (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Gage, N.L.: "Theories of teaching." (A chapter for the 1964 yearbook, several copies, various revisions.)
      Correspondence: 12/60 - 3/64.
    - New York State Annual Research Convocation., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Correspondence: 6/62 - 10/62.
    - New York University Lecture., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Gage, N.L.: "Psychological conceptions of teaching."
      Correspondence: 3/65 - 12/66.
    - Ohio State: Conference on Teacher Education., 1964 Apr (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Programs, list of participants.
    - Orange County Elementary School Administrator's Association., 1965 May (Box 2, Folder 5)
      Notes by Dr. Gage for his speech "Feedback from teachers to Principals: Does it make a difference?"
      Schedule of activities; questionnaire for participants.
    - Philadelphia desegregation., 1963 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Correspondence: 10/63.
      Clark, Kenneth: "Social science testimony in the desegregation cases."
      Van den Haag, Ernest: "Segregated schools in New York City."
      Legal brief: Anthony Chisholm, minor, vs. the Board of Public Education of Philadelphia.
    - Project Talent. (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Correspondence: 10/61 - 6/65.
    - Project Talent. Workshop., 1960, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Correspondence: 8/60 - 2/61.
    - San Diego Meeting., 1963 Dec (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Gage, N.L.: "An essay on research design for professional workers in the public schools."
      Program for workshop.
      Correspondence: 10/63 - 1/64.
      Report: "The San Diego project for the educationally and culturally disadvantaged."
    - San Diego County Department of Education., 1965 Aug (Box 2, Folder 10)
      Gage, N.L.: "Ways of analyzing teacher behavior."
      Program outline.
      Correspondence: 4/65 - 9/65.
      Receipts, bills, and travel vouchers.
    - SRA Principles of democracy test: forms A and B., 1959 Dec (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Correspondence: 3/55 - 12/59.
      "Notes on discussions of N.L. Gage with Robert Bauernfiend concerning Principles of Democracy Test."
      Copy of test; graphs of statistics of test results.
    - Social Science Research Council Conference on Personality Development in High School Youth. (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Program.
      Correspondence: 1/63 - 3/63.
      Travel voucher.
    - Social Work and Education., 1964 Apr (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Programs.
      Notes from conference.
      Correspondence: 3/65 - 6/65.
      Expense voucher.
    - SPATE (Student Personnel Association for Teacher Education) San Francisco., 1964 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Gage, N. L.: "The evaluation of teaching."
      Correspondence: 1/64 - 6/64.
    - Syracuse Conference on System Analysis and Operations Research., 1964 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Correspondence: 12/63 - 2/64.
    - UNESCO Institute for Education., 1966-67 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Correspondence: 7/66 - 10/67.
      Conference working paper: "The role of educational research in educational change."
      Lists of participants; notes on talks; tickets; travel vouchers.
    - UNESCO: Miscellaneous literature re "Role of educational research in educational change." (July 1967 conference), 1967 Jul (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Horvat, John: "Content and strategies for communication in current educational change efforts."
      Staley, Eugene: "Research and progress in the developing countries."
      Staley, Eugene: "Education's role in nation building"
      Staley, Eugene: "Strategies for educational change"
      Staley, Eugene: "Indices for groups of variables in regression analysis.
    - UNESCO: Papers by Egon Guba re July 1967 Hamburg Conference. (Box 3, Folder 7)
      "The basis for educational improvement."
      "National institute for the study of educational change."
      "A proposal for an extension of the planning grant to the National Institute for the Study of Educational Change."
      "An examination of potential change roles in education."
      "Methodological strategies for educational research."
      "Effecting change in institutions of higher education."
    - U.S. Public Health Service Fellowship Application., 1963-66 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Correspondence: 3/64 - 12/66.
      Fellowship application submitted by Dr. Gage; budget statements; grant award form.
    - U.S. Public Health Service - Mental Health Site Visit, University of Colorado., 1965 Jun (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Correspondence: 6/65 - 11/65.
      Agenda for site visit team.
      Statement of travel and expenses.
      Application for research grant, "Studies of human thought processes," submitted by Kenneth Hammond.
    - U.S. Public Health Service. Gage - Daw., 1963-65 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Application submitted to the Office of Health, Education, and Welfare by Dr. Gage.
      Correspondence: 3/63 - 12/65.
      Budget statements.
    - U.C.L.A., 1960 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Correspondence: letter dated Thanksgiving Day, 1960, which includes a list of Dr. Gage's publications.
    - University of California Medical Center Site Visit., 1965 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Gage, N.L,.: "Report of a visit to the S.F. Medical Center of the University of California on Feb. 23, 1964."
      Outline by Dr. Gage: "Research on teaching: approaches, methods, results."
      Correspondence: 1/65 - 6/65.
    - U.C.S.B. Conference., 1963 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Gage, N.L.: "A discussion of President DuBridges address on excellence in teaching."
      Program schedules.
      Correspondence: 1963.
      DuBridge, Lee: "Excellence in education."
    - University Council for Educational Administration., 1963 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Gage, N.L.: "Notes on Goal VI: producing a firmer knowledge base for school administration."
      Minutes of the Board of Trustees meeting of the U.C.E.A., Nov. 14-15, 1962.
    - University of Minnesota., 1964 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      "Research proposal submitted to the National Science Foundation by the University of Minnesota" Oct. 1964, by John Dar1et, principle investigation.
    - University of Texas., 1965 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      "A report of the Advisory Committee on Development," College of Education, University of Texas.
    - University of Utah., 1963, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      Notice of Dr. Gage's appointment as visiting professor.
      Researve book list; bookstore forms for Dr. Gage's Summer session classes at U. of Utah.
    - White House Conference on Education., 1965 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      Programs of conference; notes taken by Dr. Gage at meetings.
      Transcript of the final session of conference.
      Travel vouchers.
      Goldberg, Miriam: "Issues in education of the talented."
      Keppel, Frances: "The many issues of education."
      Tyler, Ralph: "Innovations in our schools and colleges."
      Zacharias, Jerrold: "Learning by teaching."
      Panel discussion: Educating the handicapped.
      Remarks by President Lyndon Johnson.
    - Yee Paper: Drafts 1 - 4., 1966 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      Gage, N.L., and Yee, A.H.: "Techniques for determining causal relationships between interpersonal attitudes."
      Small contract proposal submitted to the U. S. Commissioner of Education by Albert Yee.
      Questionnaires used in gathering data for study.
    - Yee Study: Split half co-efficients. (Box 4, Folder 10)
      Statistical graphs and tables to accompany the above paper.
    - Yee Study: Horst co-efficients. (Box 4, Folder 11)
      Statistical graphs and tables to accompany paper.
    - Education 413., 1955 and earlier (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Education 413: Bibliographies, prospectuses, etc. (Runkel), 1958 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Education 413: Quiz on Getzels-Thelen., 1961 Summer and Fall (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Education 413: Midsemester, final exams, and reading list., 1961 Fall (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Education 413: Final exam., 1961 Summer (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Education 413: Mid-term exam and reading list., 1963 Spring (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Education 413: Class notes. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Education 413: Ditto masters for exams. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Education 413: Tests. (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Education 413: Notes on Sherif. (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Education 391: Teaching materials, examinations, grade lists. (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Education 490: Teaching materials, examinations, grade lists. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - FILES KEPT BY DR. GAGE ON GRADUATE STUDENTS
    - Anderson, Robert (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Andre, Thomas (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Bay, Duane (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Beck, William (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Busse, Barbara (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Choy, Chungoon (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - DeKlyen, Olive (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Farrow, Ralph (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Gibbs (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Hall, Clarence (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Hansen, Duncan (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Havens, Nels (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Hill, Edward (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Hoagland, Robert (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Horowitz, Myer (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Hovenier, Peter (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Weeden (Jackson-Pownall), Diana (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Kimball, Merritt (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Matzen, Stanley (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Marr, Kenneth (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - McDonald, Kenneth (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - McFadden, Edward (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Merrill, Paul (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Michaelson, Barbara (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Misura, Dorothy (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Moegiadi (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Ostrowsky, Barnet (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Perkes, Victor (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Phelps, Jimmy (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Prince, Warren (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Pritchard, James (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Quirk, Thomas (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Sarmad, Zohrah (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Scigilligo, Pio (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Smith, Julia Ann (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Squier, Roger (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Vance, Barbara (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Van Rooijen, Louis (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Willett, J. Mensel (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - STANFORD CENTER FOR RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT IN TEACHING (SCRDT)
    - Executive Board., 1976 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Executive Board., 1975 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Executive Board., 1972-74 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Executive Board, Minutes., 1969 Mar-1973 Jan (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Administration., 1968 Mar-1976 Jun (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Job applications., 1975 Mar-1976 Apr (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Visitors., 1975-76 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Dissemination Committee., 1975 May-1975 Aug (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Elliot Eisner., 1966 Dec-1968 Jun (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Documentation Center., 1975 Apr (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - ERIC., 1975 Nov-1976 Mar (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - ERIC., 1975 Feb (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Environment for Teaching Program: Collegial evaluation materials., 1975 Jan (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Environment for Teaching Program., 1975 May-Jul (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Far West, Minicourse., 1970 Feb-1972 Feb (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - FIPSE., 1975 Jan (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Publications, Media, and Dissemination Unit, including non-NIE visitors., 1973 Jul-1976 Dec (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Media facilities., 1973 Feb (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Methodology Unit., 1976 Jan (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - National Program of Research on Teaching., 1973 Aug (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous., 1975 Feb-1976 Feb (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - General., 1971-76 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - 1971 Fall-1973 Summer (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - General., 1970 Feb-1975 May (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - USOE: Fund for Improvement of Post-Secondary Education., 1975 Jan (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - SCRDT - #4, 1969 Aug-Dec (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - SCRDT - #3, 1969 May-Jul (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - SCRDT - #2, 1969 Jan-1969 Apr (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - SCRDT - #1, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - SCRDT Guidelines for organization and operation. (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Library., 1972 Nov-Dec (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Seminars., 1965 Mar-Nov (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Government Accounting Office., 1972 Jul-1973 Jun (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Copyright and publication policy., 1971 Sep-1972 Oct (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Media Unit., 1973 Feb (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Methodology Unit., 1970 May-1972 Apr (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - National Institute of Education (NIC), 1970 Jul-1973 Jun (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - NIE: Educational Personnel Conference, 1973 Jan (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - PERT, 1967 Mar-Apr (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Proposal to establish the Center., 1965 Feb-Jul (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - California Teacher Development Project for Systems of Individualized Education., 1967 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - International Study of the Teacher's Role - correspondence & notes., 1967-68 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Program on Teaching & Linguistic Pluralism, History., 1975 Feb (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Projects: Boyer-Sowords., 1965 Oct-1966 Nov (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Projects: Cronbach., 1965 Jun-1967 Aug (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Projects: Flanders Basic Skills., 1971 Nov (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Projects: Gross., 1966 Fall-1972 dec (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Spring Review., 1972 May, Jul (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Teacher Corps Project., 1975 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Program on Teaching Effectiveness (PTE) - research assistant applications., 1973 Mar-Jun (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - R&D assistants & assistantships as of May 26, 1972., 1972 May 26 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Research assistantships. (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - empty. (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - PTE: Postdoctoral job seekers., 1971 Aug-1973 Mar (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - PTE Proposal., 1975 Aug (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - PTE: Consumer-oriented evaluation., 1972 Sep (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - PTE: Personnel responsibilities., 1976 Jun-Sep (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - PTE: Expert consultants., 1973 May-Aug (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - PTE: Joyce materials., 1974 Jan-Feb (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - PTE: Joyce, Bruce., 1974 Oct (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Microteaching., 1967 Mar-1972 Oct (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - PTE, NIE., 1972 Sep-1973 Apr (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - PTE: Report., 1972 Sep (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - PTE: Teacher Advisory Panel., 1973 Jul (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Videotape Data Bank - inventories for interns., 1967 Jun (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Intern Data Bank. (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - PTE, Work Unit 1., 1973 May-Jun (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Heur. Teach. Progr., Model Teacher Training Sys., 1970 Aug-1973 May (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Explaining Proj.: Dhar & Miltz., 1970 Feb-1972 Jun (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Explaining Proj.: Dhar & Miltz., 1970 Feb-1972 Jun (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Explaining Proj.: Dhar & Miltz., 1970 Feb-1972 Jun (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - "Explorations of the Teacher's Effectiveness in Explaining", 1970 Jul (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - PTE: Thorenson, personal competencies (Work Unit 3)., 1973 Jun (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Work Unit 3., 1974 Feb (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - PTE: Sears, Reinforcement Strategies., 1970 Oct-1972 Apr (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - P.S. Sears., 1970 jun-1973 Aug (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Protocol Proj., 1971 Jun (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Work Unit 4., 1974 Jan (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Work Unit 4 Monograph., 1973 Feb-Nov (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Heuristic Teaching: Position Papers., 1970 May (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Heuristic Group., 1969 Oct-1970 Aug (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - PTE, Koff: Logitudinal Study., 1972 Apr-Sep (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - PTE Koff: Crisis Resolution., 1972 Sep (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - PTE Koff: Group Process., 1972 Feb-Nov (Box 8, Folder 41a)
    - PTE Activity IA3 - Student Aptitude as Input and Output., 1972 Jun (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - PTE, Shavelson: Assessment System (lB), General., 1972 Apr (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - PTE, Activity 1B1 - Assessment of Teacher Performance (empty). (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - PTE - Clark - Component II - Visual Media Analysis & Dev. (empty). (Box 8, Folder 44a)
    - Heuristic Teaching Program, General., 1971 Sep-1972 Mar (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Heuristic Program Plans: Basic Program Plan., 1972 Feb (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Project 0503: Intern Data Bank., 1970 May-1971 Mar (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Joan S. Suppes., 1970 Apr-1972 Feb (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Patrick Suppes Project., 1970 Mar (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - PTE: Uncertainty Project., 1971 Aug (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - PTE: Uncertainty Project, Helen Smith Study., 1972 Mar (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - PTE Systems Analysis Model, Zifferblatt., 1971 Aug-1972 Jun (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Heuristic Teaching: Tutoring Project., 1971 Nov-1972 Oct (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Taxonomy Project., 1970 Jun (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Publications & Dissemination Unit., 1970-73 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Staff., 1970-73 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Stanford Teacher Competence Appraisal Guide (STCAG)., 1967 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Teacher in 1980 and Teaching in Small Groups., 1967 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Teaching Lab,. (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Teaching Research Instrument File., 1967-68 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Urban/Rural., 1975 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Non-Programmatic Projects., 1973 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Nat'l. Council on Educational Research., 1973 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - RESEARCH ASSISTANTS & VISITING SCHOLARS
    - SCRDT Research Assts.: general., 1967 Feb-Jun (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Anton, Jane Lee. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Barrish, Bernard: Ph.D. candidate. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Beard, Joseph W. (SUSE) (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Beckum, Leonard, qualifying exam. (SUSE) (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Bierly, Margaret. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Bruggeman, Patrick. (SUSE) (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Chang Sang Ho. (SCRDT) (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Clark, Christopher. (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Educ. 453, Spr.Qtr. (dissertation units) (SUSE) (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Directed reading, Spr.Qtr. (SUSE), 1972 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Clause, Karen E. (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Codori, Carol Anne (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Conklin, David. (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Cozine, Dean. (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Davis, John N. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - DeYoung, Alan John. (SUSE) (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Dhar, Mrs. Chandrakala. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Dhar, Chandrakala. (SUSE) (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Edwards, Ron. (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Elliott, David Haines. (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Ensz, Kathy. (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Evans, David R. (SUSE: CAGD) (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Flores-Hernandez, Maria. (SCRDT) (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Forbes, David. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Fortune, James C. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Garcia, Ronald Dan. (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Directed Reading (Educ.480) Sum.70: Geeslin, William E., 1970 Summer (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Gorth, William. (SUSE) (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Greene, David. (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Greene, Jennifer. (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Griffin, Mary Ellen. (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Hamilton, Jim. (tests for Educ.2I5) (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Holmes, Paul. (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Hubner, Judith. (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Immitt, Salvatore J. (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Jones, MiIdred. (SUSE) (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Kaiser, Bruce A. (SUSE) (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Kannegeiter, Ruthan B. (SUSE: CAGD) (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Knowles, Ruby. (Box 9, Folder 40)